weekplan.net 2019-03-16

# Privacy policy - Week Plan

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Wise Labs Pty Ltd collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the [http://weekplan.net](http://weekplan.net/) website (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Wise Labs Pty Ltd.

If you do not agree with this policy, do not access or use our Services or interact with any other aspect of our business.

## What information we collect about you

### Information you provide to us

  * account and profile information
  * content you provide through our Services
  * information you provide through our support channels
  * payment information

### Information we collect automatically

  * your use of our Services
  * device and connection information
  * cookies and other tracking technologies

### Information we receive from other sources

  * other users of the Services (may share information about you)
  * other services you link to your account (Google Calendar, Outlook, Zapier, …)

## How we use collected information

Wise Labs Pty Ltd collects and uses Users personal information for the following purposes:

  * To provide the services and personalize the user experience

We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.

  * To communicate with you about our Services

The email address Users provide for order processing, will only be used to send them information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, and/or other requests or questions. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or User may contact us via our Site.

  * To market, promote, and drive engagement with our Services
  * To improve our customer support

We use the information to get more context around the issues you submit.

  * For safety and security

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others.

Non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

### Sharing with us

Our team may gain access to your account to help resolve issues. If you want to prevent our team to access your account data, you can do so from your account settings.

### Sharing with other Service users

  * For collaboration
  * Community forums

### Sharing with third parties

  * Third-Party apps You, your administrator or other Service users may choose to add new functionality or change the behavior of the Services by enabling third party apps like Google Calendar, Outlook or Zapier.

  * Service providers We work with third-party service providers to provide website and application development, hosting, maintenance, backup, storage, virtual infrastructure, payment processing, analysis and other services for us, which may require them to access or use information about you. If a service provider needs to access information about you to perform services on our behalf, they do so under instruction from us, including abiding by policies and procedures designed to protect your information.

#### Service providers list

Name | Purpose | Country  
---|---|---  
Amazon Web Services, Inc. | Cloud Service Provider | United States  
Google Inc. | Cloud Service Provider | United Stated  
Twilio Inc. | SMS Service Provider | United Stated  
Slack Technologies, Inc | Cloud-based Communication Services | United States  
Wootric Inc. | Cloud-based Survey Services | United States  
UserEcho, LLC | Cloud-based Customer Support Services | United States  
Amplitude, Inc. | Cloud-based Analytics Services | United States  
TrackJS LLC | Cloud-based Error Tracking Services | United States  
Stripe Payments Australia Pty. Ltd | Cloud-based Payment Services | Australia  
PayPal, Inc; PayPal (Europe) Ltd | Cloud-based Payment Services | United States; United Kingdom  
Xero Limited | Cloud-based Accounting Services | New Zealand  
Facebook | Cloud-based Social Network | United States  
Zapier Inc. | Cloud Service Provider | United Stated  
  
## How we store and protect collected information

We use data hosting service providers in the United States to host the information we collect, and we use technical measures to secure your data.

All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

While we implement safeguards designed to protect your information, no security system is impenetrable and due to the inherent nature of the Internet, we cannot guarantee that data, during transmission through the Internet or while stored on our systems or otherwise in our care, is absolutely safe from intrusion by others. We will respond to requests about this within a reasonable timeframe.

### Cookies

We use cookies to help us remember that you’ve logged into our Services, understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

As you browse our Sites, advertising cookies will be placed on your computer so that we can understand what you are interested in. Our display advertising partners, then enable us to present you with retargeting advertising on other sites based on your previous interaction with us.

The techniques our partners employ do not collect personal information such as your name, email address, postal address or telephone number.

### How long is the data kept

  * account information: until you delete your account
  * information you share in the Services: even after you deactivate your account, we may retain partial information to allow other team members to continue using our Services
  * marketing information: we retain the data until you explicitly ask us to delete it

## Children

Our Services are not directed to children, and you may not use our Services if you are under the age of 18. You must also be old enough to consent to the processing of your Personal Data in your country (in some countries we may allow your parent or guardian to do so on your behalf).

## Changes to this privacy policy

Wise Labs Pty Ltd has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

## Your acceptance of these terms

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at **[[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)**
